So friends, hello, welcome to your
own channel Identity Hindi Tech.
Friends, this video is being made on VOD request, that is,
video on demand.
After a long time, we
started making videos on request,
but now it will be regular. If you want to
get your favorite video, then
what you have to do will be
explained in front of the British. But before that, let me
tell you that a person had commented,
how to get accidental insurance on the phone,
make a detailed video and
apply it live and show it, which is to be shown here for ₹1.
Now, let us tell you that
if you want to get your favorite video
on Identity Hindi Tech, then
you will not need to do much for this.
Under whatever latest video is uploaded on the channel, you can comment with your favorite
topic and say that you
want a video on it or videos related to it, then
I will make a detailed
video on it and after preparing your video as soon as possible, I will
also give the date below it, which is on
which date
this video is.  It will be uploaded
on the channel, so if you guys
want to request for video-on-demand, then whatever new video
is uploaded on the channel, you guys should comment below that video so that
your problem gets resolved as soon as possible. So
friends, let's talk
about accident insurance on the phone, where we are going to
give you information in this video with full details,
you will stay tuned till the end of the video,
friends, first of all you have to open the application on your phone,
after opening the application on the phone, you have to click on the My Money options,
you should ask for it and when you
click on it, here
in the insurance options you will
find Accident written, you have to click on this option here,
after clicking, you will
see some such interface in
which Rs. 480 is given at the top,
its value is Rs. 120 and below it Rs. 24 is given,
here the validity of Rs. 480 plan is
also for one year and the validity of Rs. 120
plan is also for one year and
here  There is also a plant bag of Rs. 24
here which is for one year but
I will tell you what is the difference between the three, the
only difference in the bags is the amount, if you
save Rs. 24 then you
get a cover of Rs. 1 lakh, if you save Rs. 120 then you
get a cover of Rs. 5 lakh
and if you take the one of Rs. 480 then you get a cover of Rs. 20 lakh so that
you get cover anywhere, let's assume you get insurance, then first of all
it is
important to know when and how you will get the money,
if let's assume that you have got the insurance,
then you do not know
how you will get the money, then why would you get insurance in the first place,
look friends, first of all I would
like to tell you that whether you get any type of
insurance, whether you get vehicle
insurance or accidental insurance or
any other
insurance, then before getting the insurance,
know the complete details about it, you people get this insurance
done and that incident happens,
how do you get the money that is covered, what process do you have to follow, so
you  First of all, I will tell people
how to get the money, when do you get it covered,
and what process will you have to go through.
See, friends, if we talk about accident insurance, then
here the curved
money is available in a different type of condition.
Friends, we would like to tell you that let's assume
that a person has taken accident
insurance and it is
printed, then in such a situation, if
he dies due to an accident, then the
full amount of the cover is given to him,
rather, he gets this amount as he normally lives,
but let's do it
on his accident, but here, if
he becomes disabled, like his leg is broken
or his hand is broken, then in such a situation,
he gets the amount of the cover,
so let's first talk about
how you will get it. Here, by
clicking on the rs. 24 one, we would like to tell you the details,
let's click on the rs. 24 one,
after that we clicked on get policy,
after clicking on the policy,
this type of interface is visible here
where our name is written above,
email  Address because the email address that I have on your phone is the same as the one that is
flipped here,
you can change it if you want, see the
accident in Suresh is the
call on the phone here, it is actually from ICICI Lombard
but you can buy the phone's Bhaiya, first of all it is
written Viv at the top,
then let's click on the benefit and it will show,
see the same two things are mentioned in the benefit
which we have told you a while ago, the
cover amount here is one lakh
rupees, you can see it is 1 lakh rupees, another
small question might be arising in your mind
that if we assume that an
accident etc. happens here, then
what process will we have to do to get the cover amount, so
we will tell you about this in detail too,
see you will not have to call on the phone
nor will you have to contact them through the phone, you
can directly call ICICI Lombard, I have put its contact number of
ICICI Lombard
in the description box of the video, if
you want, note  You can also call them
and claim by calling there,
you will get the amount mentioned
but there is also some verification process
which they verify in their own way,
after that they give you this cover amount, so
now let us talk about
how you can complete this insurance,
how
can it come, let me tell you that
you will get every type of accidental insurance
or whatever insurance is done, there are
different plans in different companies,
so here is the
plan of Rs. 24, so let me first
tell you that if you want, you
can also set the term and condition here, since
time in condition is given here, by
clicking there you can also create the statement condition,
now here the
premium that you make in Rs. 24
becomes Rs. 20.34 paisa premium and if we
talk about GST here, then ₹3.66 paisa
GST is taken from you, that is, in total
You have to pay Rs 24, so here
you have to enter normal information like your
date of birth, normally you will have to
submit the details here in any case,
normally you will have to add it, you will have to
enter the name of the nominee, after that
you will have to click on the option while agreeing to the timer condition, keep a little
care, if your age is 18 years or
more than 18 years and
less than 65 years, then you will be
able to take the insurance now, we have
entered all the details here, I would like to tell you
that you must read the term and condition once,
this is a very
big term and condition, if we start
explaining it in this video then this video will become very
long, so you
must read the quarter light condition, so
after reading the term and condition, you have to
agree to the temple condition here,
after agreeing, you have to click on the back office,
when you click on the payment voucher,
on the pay office, then here  You
can also make payment through debit card, credit card or BHIM UPI. Let us
show you how to make a payment here.
After entering the UPI PIN through UPI, you have to confirm the payment from here. The
payment has been confirmed and you
can see that the purchase has also been made. Now
two options are available here - View Detail and
New Policy. If you
want to see the policy, you can see it by clicking on Vivo Policy.
If you want to click on View Detail, that is, you
want to see the payment that was made, then you
can see it by clicking on the YouTube channel. So we will
click on this policy here. Now let
us come to the policy.
After clicking on the policy, you can see here that it is dated
18th August 2002, which is
said to be valid till 17th August 2018 and it is
written 'Active' here. Friends, if we talk about this document, then
here comes the document section, by
clicking on it
you enter your email address and
then click on send. The
document is received on your email address.  The
policy certificate number will be shown to you at the top,
which is the policy certificate
number, it will be shown to you by
clicking on insured details, you can see
your name here i.e. the name of the person in whose name this
policy has been taken,
along with this you can see the name of the nominee here, you
can also see the email address, friends,
here you get label options
but it is not clicking on it, here you
can see an i button on the side,
click on it and here you will be told with complete details
how you can do it and friends,
I had already told you that to make a claim
you will have to directly
call ICICI Lombard whose number
is 1800 226 which you can also see written, so the
same things are written here
that you people should
call ICICI Lombard, so now
friends, the biggest question in this is that
which documents will be required at the time of making a claim,
we will tell you that also, see
here if there is a death then you will get this
Deep comment is listed, from this you will have to give the
document, if let's assume that something happens to the brain here, then
in such a situation you will have to give the document written below,
here make it
clear in the biggest detail that the
death has happened naturally and not in an accident, then
in such a situation you will
not get any amount, that is, you people
will think that we have got accidental
insurance here and if we pay naturally then we will get
some money, then yes you will
not get it at all, you will get it
only on accidental death or if you become
centrally disabled, you will get it only then,
we have told you with full details in this video, we hope that you
people liked this video, if you liked the video then
like and share the video
and to get similar videos,
definitely subscribe to the channel, if you have
any question related to this video then do
not forget to comment below the video, we will see you
but please give us permission in this video, till then
good for a day